{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Our_Daily_Bread__1934_film_",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor created the film Our Daily Bread (1934).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7427613139152527,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6053868532180786,
            "question": "Who directed the film Our Daily Bread?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5406246185302734,
            "question": "What impact did Our Daily Bread have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5262039303779602,
            "question": "What year was Our Daily Bread released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4851066768169403,
            "question": "What genre might the film Our Daily Bread belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47821131348609924,
            "question": "Is Our Daily Bread a fictional or non-fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41612508893013,
            "question": "Did King Vidor direct any other notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34491315484046936,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Our Daily Bread?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30863338708877563,
            "question": "What themes or messages might Our Daily Bread explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2805464565753937,
            "question": "Can you find any reviews or critical analysis of Our Daily Bread?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor created the film Our Daily Bread (1934).",
            "html": "yago_21633_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes or messages might Our Daily Bread explore?",
            "html": "yago_21633_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in Our Daily Bread?",
            "html": "yago_21633_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did King Vidor direct any other notable films?",
            "html": "yago_21633_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_157.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21633_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that King Vidor directed and co-wrote the film \"Our Daily Bread\" (1934)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support that King Vidor directed the film \"Our Daily Bread\" released in 1934. Therefore, the statement that King Vidor created the film \"Our Daily Bread\" (1934) is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}